Guide to the Mark Bloch Postal Art Network (PAN) Archive MSS.170
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Serials, 1972-2007
  - CineVue [vol. 1 no. 1, 2; vol. 4 no. 2], 1986; 1989 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Coagula #20, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Collective Farm, undated (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Comedy Gazette [vol. 1 no. 2], December 1991 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Comic Shop News Spring Preview, undated (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Computer Graphics World, January 2001 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Computer Pictures, March-April 1994 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Contagion #5, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - Context #8, undated (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - ContreCiel #2, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - Convulsions Zine, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Cool'eh [vol. 2 no. 1], 2004 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - Counterspeed #6, undated (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - Creatif Art Revue #64, undated (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - Creedences 8/9 [vol. 3], 1980 (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - Cultural Correspondence, Summer 1985 (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - Cultural Democracy #39, Spring 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Cutthroat Reissue #1, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Daily News, August 17, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - D.A.P. Books on Contemporary Culture, Fall 1996 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Death of Vinyl, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Desert, November 1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Dirt #4, Spring 1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Discoveries Through Inner Quests, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - The Divorcee, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Doc Whiz! Lost in Kent, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Downtown #177, January 17, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Dreamtime [#3; #4; #5; #7], 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Drift Distribution Catalog [#1; #2], 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Drive-By Book #3, March 23, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Ear [vol. 3 no. 10], February 1989 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Echoing Sentiments, 1989-1992 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Ed's Magazine of Community Correspondence, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Egalité Ego Light, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Elefant Art Zine, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Elvis in Hell by Donna Tartt, undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Erased deKooning Drawings by Mike Bidlo, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Escuela Social de Zaragoza, August 1975 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Experimental MIX [vol. 12], 1998 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Fact Sheet Five #45, undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Fandangos, [1982] (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Farm Pulp #13, April-May 1992 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Fiji Times 2 by Carol Stetser, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Fine Art Network [#68; #82], undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Flash Art, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Foundation for Life Action Books & Tapes, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - The Fourth Folding Cigar, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Framework [vol. 6 no. 2], 1993 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Freedom Catalog, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Frederic C. Beil Bodies in Print, Spring 1985 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Friour #2, March 2003 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Front, March-April 1991 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Full Plate and Blue Darter by Jack Saunders, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Galántai, October 2-November 10, 1988; September 2-October 8, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Gallery Guide, 1989; 2006 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - The Gathering of the Tribes of the Earth, undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Global Mail #13, January-April 1996 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Godzilla Newsletter, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Guggenheim Guide, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Guidebook for the 90s, Fall-Winter 1988 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Hacker Art Books, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Hacker-Stranf Art Books Catalog, undated (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Haint Digest [vol. 3, 4], October 1984 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Happy Kitty [#2; #3], Summer 1995; Fall 1995 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Heresy, Thanks!, undated (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Himalayan Institute, Summer 1995 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Homo Futurus, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Hosteling, November-December 1989 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Hvedekorn #2, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Ignite [#8; #9], 1995 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Il Tempo, Il Luogo, L'Opera, May 17-June 26, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - Impress #1, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - Incredible Inquiry Catalog #7, undated (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Indie, July-August 1998; September-October 1998 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Information Sickness #6, December 1994 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Intelligent Agent [vol. 1 no. 5], September 1996 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - The Interactive Music Monthly, April-May 1993 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Interface, Winter 1985 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - Iron Feather Journal II, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - The Inside Connection [vol. 1 no. 12], November 1998 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - J'amo #4, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - Java Journal [vol. 1 no. 1; vol. 1 no. 4], February 1994; June 1994 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - Joey Auto Matic by Robert W. Howington, June 3, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Just Another Menace to Society, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - Juxtaposition Vol. 2, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Kababatic Wind by Berty Skuber, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - Kidstamps, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - Kidstamps 1987-1988 Supplement (Box 43, Folder 69)
  - K Newsletter #4, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - Knitting Factory Knotes, November-December 1994; July-August 1996; September-October 1990; May-June 2001 (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - K.O. im Copyshop by Robert W. Howington, undated (Box 43, Folder 72)
  - K Records News, undated (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - The Kripalu Experience Calendar and Program Guide, October 1990-January 1991 (Box 43, Folder 74)
  - Labor Notes #307, October 2004 (Box 43, Folder 75)
  - Laissez Faire Book, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 76)
  - The L Magazine, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 77)
  - La Poire D'Angoisse #10, undated (Box 43, Folder 78)
  - L'Chaim [#212; #713], April 17, 1992; April 5, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - The Learning Annex, January-February 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - The Letter Exchange, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - LCD, WFMU Program Guide, 1988-1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Loisada [vol. 11 no. 2], March-April 1988 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - The Love Tapes, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - The Lower East Side Visitor's Guide [vol. 1 no. 2], Fall 1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council: Downtown Arts Activits Calendar [vol. 12 no. 1, 6; vol. 16 no. 5; vol. 18 no. 1, 7; vol. 19 no. 1], January; June 1989; February 1993; October 1994; April 1995; October 1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Madi's Mail Club [unnumbered; #9], 1988; Fall 1990 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Maximum Rock n Roll #72, May 1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Merkin Concert Hall, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Metro Riquet #6, January 1989 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Partial Periodicals, 1994; 2002 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Midnight Times #27, undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Miller Theatre Catalog, Columbia University, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Minnesota Explorer, Spring-Summer 1986 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - MJB 90 1991 Catalog of Cassette, November 1991 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Movement Research: Performance Journal #6, Spring-Summer 1993 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - MTV Present: The Human Rights Watch Film Festival, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - MSRRT Newsletter [vol. 9 no. 1], February 1996 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Musea #35, July 1995 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - The Museum of Television and Radio, May 28-November 20, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Music, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - The Music News [vol. 3 no. 2], April-May 1992 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - The Nation, February 5, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - National Museum of the American Indian, Fall 2005 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - National Stampagraphic #3, April 1983 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - National Stampagraphic [vol. 4 no. 2], January 1986 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - ND #9, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - The Netletter [vol. 1 no. 87, 88], undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Newark Press [vol. 2 no. 2], 1983 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - New Route #5, Spring 1989 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - New Wilderness Letter, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - The New York Records Review [vol. 1 no. 3], Summer 1990 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts [vol. 3 no. 1], Fall 2004 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - New York Press [vol. 3 no. 2], January 12, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Next Wave Festival BAM, 1992; 1996 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Nexus Press, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - No Business As Usual, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Norbert Koschitz, undated (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Noticias de Cooper Square [vol. 1 no. 1], October 1997 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Now What, Spring 1989 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - NY Arts International Edition [vol. 5 no. 5], April 2000 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - NYU Today [vol. 4 no. 1], September 12, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - On the Line, September 1986 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Opera News [vol. 46 no. 7], December 19, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Open World, undated (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Overload Version 8.0, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - P.A.I.N. Music, November 1998 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Panmag #8, July 1984 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Panmag #29 Network Mutation, July 1990 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Panmag, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Parallel Discussions: Amsterdam-Bevlin, undated (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Parallel--International Creative Magazine, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Phosphorusflourish #20, undated (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Photostatic #11, May 1985 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Piece of Licorice and Other White Elephants, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Planet Roc [vol. 2 no. 6, 7], June 1990; July-August 1990 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Plague [vol. 2 no. 2, 3], 1988 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Playbills, 1987-1997 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - The Poet Tree [vol. 11 no. 1], 1992 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - The Poetry Project Newletter #20, February/March 2007 (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Pop Smear Magazine, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Post Hype [vol. 2 no. 5], 1983 (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Printed Matter Catalogs, 1994-1996 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Prix Arts Electrionica, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Processed World #12, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Prop [no. 6, 7, 9/10], April 1981; December 1981; July 1983 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - The Psychic Guide Book Shop Catalog, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - Public Art Review [issue 10 vol. 5 no. 2], Spring-Summer 1994 (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Public Property, Fall 1985 (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Pulp #13, September-October 1994 (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Push-Button Controller #3, Spring 1992 (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Pyramid Magazine, September 1988 (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Ragged Edge Press Irreverant Rubber Stamp Catalog and Rubber Stamp Supplement, 1995-1998 (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - Radio Riot #23, May 1993 (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Rectificación Número 12, October 1996 (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Remembering Bob Scobey and his Frisco Band, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - Renta Conceptual Artist Zine, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - ReR, September 1989; February 1999 (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - Research in Art and Telecommunication, January 24, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Rock & Roll Hall of Fame, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - Rubber Bizzaro Stamps, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Rubber Stamps of America, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Rubber Stamp Archive, undated (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Ruggero Maggi, undated (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Samaya Foundation [vol. 1 no. 1], Spring 1990 (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Savage #5 by Robert W. Howington, undated (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Scanline: The Newsletter of Downtown Community Television Center, May-June 1992 (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - See Hear Speak, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - Shoe Polish Week, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 84)
  - Shooshka Stampworks, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - Short, April 1987 (Box 44, Folder 86)
  - The Shy Man's Way: Homosexuality in Perspective, March 1985 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Simon Says, Silencio = Muerte, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Simon Says [vol. 5, 6, 9], November 1996; January 1997; February 1997; May 1997 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Simon Says [vol. 3 no. 1, 2, 3, 4], 1998 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Simon Says [vol. 3 no. 5, 6, 8, 9; vol. 4 no. 1, 4], 1999 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - SLF #2, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Small Press Distributions, Fall-Winter 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Smile [vol. 64], May 31, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 8, Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Smile Magazine #10, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Smithsonian [vol. 17 no. 12], March 1987 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Snarl, Fall 1988 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - The Sneak, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Soloflex, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Sony Workshops, Spring-Summer 1992 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Sound Choice #11, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Sound Views, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Spark [vol. 1 no. 54], September 1992-March 1993 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Spiked Slurpee by Robert W. Howington, February 16, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - The Sporadical [#2; #8], undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Stroker #38, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Sunday: The Plain Dealer, May 19, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Sunday Magazine, March 12, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Sunstorm, July 1988; December 1988 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Sunstorm, July 1989; September-October 1989; November 1989 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Sunstorm, September-October 1989; December 1989 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Sunstorm, Summer 1990; October 1990 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Sup #2, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Super Book, Spring 1994 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Surf Guide, September 1964 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Surfing, February 1980; July 1982 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Surfing [vol. 16 no. 12; vol. 19 no. 4], December 1980; April 1983 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Surfing, February 1991; September 1991; October 1991; November 1991 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Surfing Calendar, 1981; 1990 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Sweater #9, October-November 1998 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - The Sword That Cuts, The Fire That Burns, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Temse Ponton, undated (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Tenth Assembling, undated (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Texas Beat [issue 101 vol. 4 no. 6], April 16, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Timeless Light, January 1984 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Top Drawer Rubber Stamps, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - True Dada Confessions, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Typing Out the Dead by Bill Shields, July 24, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - UCI Fine Arts: Expressions [vol. 2 no. 1], Fall 1991 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - United Nations Publications, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Umbrella [vol. 9 no. 2; vol. 10 no. 1], October 1986; April 1987 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Unowned Words, undated (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - The Usual Suspects by Robert W. Howington, August 25-19, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Urban Rag #10, March 1989 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Vagabond: White Paper Series [2nd Installment], 1984 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Vagabond White Paper #5, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Viscomm '95 Showguide, November 2-4, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Weast, [1989] (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - The Weirdorama, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Weird Smut Comics #2, [1987] (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - We Puked Together in a Rusty Tub: Charles Bukowski's Best, undated (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - WFMU Catalog of Curiosities, Summer 1995 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - What? #7, Fall 1985 (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - White Pine Press Catalog, Spring-Fall 1989 (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - White Girl Witch Tits by Robert W. Howington, undated (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, September-November 2002 (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Wire [vol. 3 no. 2], May 1987 (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - Writer's Block #4, Spring-Summer 1989 (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - Writers and Book Catalog, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 61)
  - Zeitgeist, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Zona, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 62)
  - Zone, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 63)
  - [Untitled], [1985] (Box 45, Folder 64)
  - [Untitled, Edited by Dazar], April 28, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 65)
  - [Untitled], undated (Box 45, Folder 66)
  - [Untitled], undated (Box 45, Folder 67)
  - [Untitled], undated (Box 45, Folder 68)
- Series V: Books, 1976-2006
  This series consists of the books in the collection.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - "April Fool's," He Said by ROAM!, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 1982, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - All My Rubber Stamps by Mark Pawson, August 2, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Bui in Sala by Rita Vitaki Rosati. Text by Giorgio Bonomi., October 28, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Collective Copy, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Common Sense by Jack Saunders, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - The Death of the Cowboy, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Reactions '78-'03 Stage One: 1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Farmers of the Culture, December 1988 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Fractaled Fields and Fairytales: A Non Linear Look at Culture by Jeff Brice, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - The Great Lover and the Little One, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Hemisa Book, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Hiroshima Mon Amour, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Images and Other Projects by Jan Henderikse, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - In a Small Frame MAŁEJ RAMCE by Jürgen O. Olbrich, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Interactions, December 2, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Introduction Book by John M. Bennett, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - It As It by Michael Andre, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Journal to Stella by Jack Saunders, undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - A Key to Milan, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Kunstgartenschau, undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Less Newspoems by Tuli Kupferberg, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - A Life of Secrets by Kim Jones, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Mark's Little Book About Kinder Eggs by Mark Pawson, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - My Life In Show Biz by Steve Carter, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Myself Resolved: An Artist's Experience with Lymphoma by Darcy Lynn, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Neo Phobe a novel nby Jim Feast with Ron Kolm, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - York City Yansformations, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - The Peel by John M. Bennett, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Picasso, Marlon Vito Post Nico Classics, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Piece of Licorice & Other White Elephants by Sam Scotland, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Pith: Looking for Wordless Lines, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Political Satire: Post Scriptum by Vittore Baroni, September 1979 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Por La Paz, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Post Kunst USA, July 10, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Pre K, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Random Dates by Tom Warren, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Rat Piece by Kim Jones, February 17, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Rock & Roll Hall of Fame: The Tenth Annual Induction Dinner, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Rubber Stamp Show, October 18-November 18, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Screed by Jack Saunders, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Siggraph '83, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Stampel, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Tears of the Soul by L.D. Lee, undated (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Underground Culture Vulture #10 [CD-R], undated (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - The Vulnerability of Order by Martine Bellen, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - The Zone by David Chelsea, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - [Untitled] by Steen Møller Rasmussen, undated (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - [Untitled], undated (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - [Untitled], undated (Box 46, Folder 51)
- Series VI: Personal, 1983-2005
  This series contains personal material that documents Mark Bloch's life.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by folder title. Folder titles were devised by the archivist.
  - [Art Supplies], 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - ["Bogus Requests For Mail'], 1992 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - [Cards, Announcements, and Programs] [1 of 2], 1983-2004 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - [Cards, Announcements, and Programs] [2 of 2], 1983-2004 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Contracts, 1992; 2006 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - New York University, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Receipts, 1992; 2005 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Series VII: Junk Mail, 1980-2007
  Series retains its original order at donation.
  - General Junk Mail Box I, 1980-2007 (Box 31)
  - General Junk Mail Box II, 1980-2007 (Box 32)
  - General Junk Mail Box III, 1980-2007 (Box 33)
  - General Junk Mail Box IV, 1980-2007 (Box 34)
  - General Junk Mail Box V, 1980-2007 (Box 35)
  - General Junk Mail Box VI, 1980-2007 (Box 36)
  - General Junk Mail Box VII, 1980-2007 (Box 37)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Junk Mail, 1980-2007
  This series consists of the same materials as Series II: Junk Mail.
  Material in this series was separated due to size, and mirrors the arrangement in Series II: Junk Mail.
  - Subseries A: Sorted
    - Arts Calendars, 1985-2005 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Aktion Weihnachtspostkarte [Exhibition Poster, Germany], undated (Folder 3 Right)
    - Art Exhibition Posters, 1981-1994 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - "Black Box" A Film by Beth B & Scott B [Poster], 1978 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Fine Art Network Issue #9D-1 (#55), [1990] (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Ko De Jonge [Middelburg, Holland], January 1991 (Folder 2 Right)
    - "Leningrad's 'Experiment' Theater in Avant-Garde-Arama" PS 122 [Poster], April 14-15 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council's Downtown: Arts Activities Calendars, 1987; 1992; 1994; 1995 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Mail Art Exhibitions, 1987-1992 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Mail Art Exhibition Materials, 1993 (Folder 4 Right)
    - NYC Poetry Calendars, 1985-1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Objects, 1979-2005
  This series contains the same type of material in Series III: Objects.
  Material in this series was separated due to size, and mirrors the arrangement in Series III: Objects.
  - "Miseria" by Antonio Pérez-Cares F. [Santiago, Chile - Print on Canvas], undated (Flat-file-folder 2, Object ID: 170.2.0060)
  - "Señor Diputado" by Antonio Pérez-Cares F. [Santiago, Chile - Print on Canvas], undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
- OVERSIZE: Series IV: Serials, 1972-2007
  This series contains the same type of material as Series IV: Serials.
  Material in this series was separated due to size, and mirrors the arrangement in Series IV: Serials.
  - 7 Days New York [vol. 3 no. 7], February 21, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Artists' Publications in Print 82, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Art Attack, November 1985 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Art Speak [vol. 17 no. 6], April 1995 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Art Times [vol. 9 no. 9], May 1993 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - BAM, August-September 1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Beef [vol. 5 no. 15, 16, 17], 1985 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Beef [vol. 6 no. 18, 19, 20], 1986 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Between the Lines [vol. 1 no. 2], Winter 1997 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Bizzaro [no. 12, 15, 16], 1985-1987 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Bizarro Rubber Stamp Catalog [no. 13 & 14], 1986 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Boog City #4, March 11-25, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Bookmarks [vol. 1 no. 1, 2], June 1991 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Catharsis Monthly, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Chakra #3, Spring 1987 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Choices: The Human Development Magazine, August 1999 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - CineVue [vol. 1 no. 3, 4; vol. 2 no. 5], September 1989; November 1986; November 1987 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - CineVue [vol. 3 no. 1, 2; vol. 3 no. 3], March 1988; June 1988; September 1988 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - CineVue [vol. 3 no. 4; vol. 4 no. 1, 3], December 1988; March 1989; September 1989 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Coagula #8, Autumn 1993 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - CDF [Colorado Dance Festival], 1994 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Cover, March 1989; April 1990 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - DT 5 [Incomplete], April 15, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Discorder #123, April 1993 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Downtown [no. 141, 144, 148], April 12-19, 1989; May 3-10, 1989; May 31-June 7, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Downtown [no. 190, 209; Partial Issues], January 1990; April 11-18, 1990; July 11-18, 1990; September 12-19, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Ear [vol. 2 no. 1], August-September 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)